We want the Lord to expose among us those spirits that kill, steal and destroy.
Holy Ghost fire!
Say, out!
When the fire of the Holy Ghost fell during the mass prayer of the first service,
arresting many who are possessed by evil spirits, was this man.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
In the second service, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, furthered his deliverance
with a prophetic revelation.
Let us listen to the prophecy and its confirmation.
I see the involvement of a human being to make a charm
and that charm has become a demon.
It is in your house as I'm talking now.
Yes, sir.
My name is Tony.
When I had a problem I was initiated with a concotion.
The concotion comes to meet me every night in Lagos here.
It comes like a human being, calling my name and speaking with me
like a human being.
He will tell me what he wants, telling me that he needs such and such things.
I should bring them for him and I would do that.
The reason why he is running now is that he is afraid; they are getting very close to him.
He abandoned the house and he is now looking for somebody who can save him.
The demon is chasing him.
The concotion has become a human being.
It appears to you?
Yes, sir.
Physically?
One of the reasons God gives us His power is to confirm that
we are speaking for Him.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ, out!
Following the prophetic message given to Mr Anthony Nnemeka last Sunday,
the man of God gave him Anointing Water and instructed him in the name of Jesus
to go to the village and bring the charm.
This is the place where the charm the man of God prophecied about last Sunday is.
This is where it is in my village.
This is where I kept the charm.
This is the Anointing Water that the man of God gave to me to spray
on the charm and bring it to Lagos.
I command you to be destroyed in the name of Jesus.
This is the black cloth that used to cover it.
In line with the word of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
I command you to be destroyed in the name of Jesus.
This is the 'juju' (charm), the pot and everything.
This is the pot used for the sacrifice.
I never came here for the sacrifice.
I used to send people because the charm is very powerful.
This is the Anointing Water.
I command you to be destroyed in the name of Jesus.
Look at the smoke!
Smoke is coming out!
The power is going out.
The spirit is going out.
That smoke is a demon going away.
You see a pot but it is a demon.
Let's watch.
In the name of Jesus.
Jesus! You see the smoke going out. Jesus!
I'm afraid because the spirit is going out.
Eh! Chineke (God)!
Jesus!
My hand is being shocked!
In the name of Jesus, I command you to go out!
In the name of Jesus!
Prophet T.B. Joshua sent me to destroy you with the Anointing Water
and I hereby destroy you in the name of Jesus.
You must be destroyed in the name of Jesus.
I command every power in you to be destroyed, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
You must go to Lagos, in the name of Jesus.
If not for God, I would not have been able to carry it.
It is very powerful.
But in the name of Jesus, every power in the thing is destroyed.
Thank You, Jesus.
Anthony Nnemeka arrives at The SCOAN with the charm.
He has come back for his final deliverance.
Thank God for the grace! Thank You, Jesus!
The purpose of watching this programme is for others to see and know that
there is refuge - Jesus is the refuge.
My name is Tony from Anambra State.
I was the one the man of God prophesied to last Sunday
that I have a charm in the village.
Yes, I'm the one.
It happened that when I had a problem, I went to a herbalist.
The herbalist said that he would prepare a charm for me.
After preparing the charm, he asked me to carry it to my house in the village
and keep it there and I did that.
I kept the charm in the village and came back to Lagos.
The charm always came and met me, the demon always came and met me in Lagos
and told me to come and sacrifice something like a dog or chicken and I would do that.
After doing that, I realised that the charm was destroying my family.
I decided to go for deliverance.
One day, I was watching Emmanuel TV.
I saw the way Prophet T.B. Joshua was delivering people
and I then decided to come to this place.
The night that I decided to come to this place, the demon came to meet me at midnight
and told me that as he was killing people, did I know that he can also kill me.
I asked him, "Why? What have I done?"
He did not answer me and left. That was before I came here last week Sunday.
Last week Sunday, the man of God prophesied to me.
This is me and the charm is also here.
The man of God gave me Anointing Water to go to my village,
spray it on the charm and bring it to Lagos State. I then went.
In the process of spraying the Anointing Water, smoke began to come out of the charm.
I was very scared because the charm is very powerful.
After spraying the Anointing Water, the smoke stopped.
As I wanted to put the charm into the bag, the charm began to shock my hand.
I began to pray and sprayed the Anointing Water on my hand, then it stopped.
Then I put the charm into the bag and brought it to Lagos.
Man of God, the charm is outside.
The worst of sin can be forgiven
Are your sins so grave or small
This is where we put the things sacrificed to the charm.
The charm was for my protection.
Through this charm, I was initiated.
Get the Anointing Water.
Just take the carton there. Let him take one out of it.
Okay. We need to sanctify the two hands.
Man of God said that the Anointing Water should be given to the man
for total separation from this demonic charm.
As you can see on the screen of your television set.
A newcomer there, please come.
Follow her to that place and give her Anointing Water.
Let her spray this Anointing Water on both hands.
Let us see what will happen to the man.
The Anointing Water we are going to collect today will be sprayed on both hands
which the man used to carry this demonic charm
so that we all can see the manifestation of the mighty power.
Just pick one out of it.
Watch the screen. The woman is picking the Anointing Water from the carton,
opening it, bringing it out and is about to unseal the Anointing Water bottle.
The Man of God has given her the instruction of what to do.
That she should ask the man to stretch out both hands
and she should spray the Anointing Water on both hands of the man.
On both hands, in the name of Jesus.
Be free in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Be free in Jesus' name!
Responding to the power in the Anointing Water.
See what is happening to the man.
He can no longer hold himself. See what is happening to him.
Spinning around.
We can see what is happening to him now.
Down he goes.
Ok. Go near to him and spray his hands on the floor.
Watch the screen and see what is happening to the man,
immediately the Anointing Water touched his hands.
You can see what is happening to him right now -
shaking uncontrollably.
And shout the name Jesus, Madam.
In the name of Jesus!
That is deliverance. Watch your screen.
Give thanks to God for what the Lord has done in our lives today
and for what you have seen.